

# Yury Kastsen

- +48881096343
- spkava@gmail.com
- Wrocław

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/kastsen">https://www.linkedin.com/in/kastsen</a>

Website: <a href="https://mental.gatsbyjs.io">https://mental.gatsbyjs.io</a>
Github: <a href="https://github.com/kastsen">https://github.com/kastsen</a>

#### Introduction

I assist clients in bringing their concepts to life, ensuring projects are launched on time. Programming, product support and enhancement all fall within my scope of responsibilities. I hope that the world can undergo changes, so I always endeavor to connect my work and life with progressive projects.

My technology stack includes: JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, Node.js, Webpack, Pixi.js, Create.js, Three.js, Gatsby.js, HTML5, Pug.js, CSS3, SCSS, Bash, Git and more.

I'm now looking forward to using my skills and experience in a fulfilling position.

## **Experience**

12/2022 - until now Web Games Developer

**QS** Games

Web Games Development and maintenance service:

- · CORAL ISLE 2 https://coralisle2.guartsoft.com/index.html
- · FARLAND https://farland.quartsoft.com/index.html
- · PAPAYA https://papaya.quartsoft.com/index.html
- · Skills: JavaScript · Typescript · Webpack · Pixi JS · Create JS · React · Redux ·

HTML5 · Git · mySQL · REST API

03/2020 - 08/2022 Playable Ads Developer

Vizor Games

Playable ads development. Framework development and support. Build automatisation. Optimization of processes and tasks, work with the team. Skills: Node.js  $\cdot$  npm  $\cdot$  Webpack  $\cdot$  JavaScript  $\cdot$  Matter JS  $\cdot$  Bash  $\cdot$  Pixi.js  $\cdot$  Spine Animations  $\cdot$  Tiled  $\cdot$  HTML5  $\cdot$  SVN  $\cdot$  JSON  $\cdot$  ES6+

12/2019 - 03/2020 Front-end Developer

Bamboo Apps

Project support and maintenance service. Interviews, onboarding for new employees. Skills: JavaScript · Node.js · Express.js · mySQL · CSS3 · SCSS ·

 $\mathsf{SPA} \cdot \mathsf{UI} \cdot \mathsf{Github} \cdot \mathsf{Webpack} \cdot \mathsf{Git} \cdot \mathsf{SASS} \cdot \mathsf{AJAX} \cdot \mathsf{Cascading} \ \mathsf{Style} \ \mathsf{Sheets} \ (\mathsf{CSS})$ 

· npm · ES6+ · API · Pug.js

05/2019 - 05/2020 Front-end Development Speaker

School MyFreedomIT

Skills: Public Speaking · CSS3 · HTML5 · Git · Bootstrap · JavaScript

02/2018 - 11/2019 Front-end Developer

Logic Software Inc.

Work with a team, including a team of designers, developers and marketing. June training. Support and optimization of the project. Skills: Node.js · JavaScript · CSS3 · SCSS · React · Web Design · Agile Methodologies · Scrum · UX · jQuery · Webpack · Git · SASS · AJAX · JSX · Cascading Style

Sheets (CSS) · JSON · npm · Yarn · ES6+ · API · PHP · mySQL

06/2015 - 12/2017 Web Development Specialist

inAweb

Web sites design, development and support. Building custom WordPress

themes and plugins.

05/2012 - 08/2014 Content management, HTML-markup

**Daily News Portal** 

Content management, web-administrator, HTML-markup.

# Knowledge and skills

Languages:

Russian (proficient) Byelorussian (proficient) English (intermediate) Czech (pre-intermediate) Polish (pre-intermediate)

Skills:



### **Education**

Level of education

University

2015 - 2016

Erasmus+ EVS
Politologie

2008 - 2012

BSPU
Philology. Journalism

# **Certification and courses**

2019 **School MyfreedomIT** Javascript, React JS. Front-end Development

2013 Používání vizuálních symbolů a tvůrčích přístupů

Prague

Známost s českou zkušeností v použití vizuálních symbolů a kreativních

přístupů k sociální činnosti.

### **Hobbies**

Music Nature Quad roller skating